A souvenir?
Yes, we went to
a hot spring the other day!
Here. Please enjoy it with
the others at your agency!
STRAWBERRY - PLAIN
CHOCOLATE - GREEN TEA
- Hot springs pudding!
Which should I take?!
Glad you managed to get
a hot springs date out of your work.
Th-The work came first, though...
Even though you had to
reschedule things here?
W-Well, we did manage
to solve the case...
Hey, Kikira, you don't
want one? Maybe later?
He likes green tea flavor?
Hey, sorry I'm late!
We just got here, too!
Good evening!
Sorry, it took me longer
than I expected to get out...
Akira-san said you were having
trouble collecting evidence.
Is everything all right now?
Ah, yeah... That's what
had me late again today.
You want me to find
evidence in all this garbage?
Sorry. I didn't realize it would be
so much either...
But I really need evidence
for this case, so...
Sorry it's all so sudden. I can ask
another agency if you need me to.
I didn't say I wouldn't do it.
Man, this sucks.
When do you need it by?
Oh, well...
I have a meeting
with the client in two days...
Talk about a rush job.
I'm really sorry!
You're amazing, Daichi!
You found the evidence in
that garbage heap this quickly?
You're amazing! Thank you!
Calm down. You're
gonna pick up the stink.
I fell in love all over again!
Kikira-san's amazing, isn't he?
He's serious about that stuff, at least.
Don't tell Daichi
I was gushing about him, okay?
He's a lucky guy.
Can't believe a sourpuss like him found
a partner who really gets him.
Yeah, yeah!
Jarashi-san, you haven't
met someone who gets you?
What's this now?
You have someone you like?
I wouldn't say that. We're just
kind of on the same wavelength...
Makes it easy to be myself.
You mean the one from the clothing shop?
Yeah, yeah! That clerk I told you about.
I've had a ton of fun
choosing outfits since we met.
Yes, I see.
It's important to have
someone like that in your life.
Yeah!
When you have an interest in common,
you can talk about anything!
Jarashi-san, you've been acting different
since the two of you met.
- Really?
- Yes. You've been so calm and peaceful.
I guess life does get easier
when you've got less on your mind!
Lucky girl!
Speaking of, how are things
for you in that area lately, Shizuka?
Sounds like you and Tonome
are still getting along.
We're currently planning
our cohabitation!
Look at you, making it happen!
And soon,
CELEBRATE!! AKIRA-SAN'S FIRST SLEEPOVER!
- Akira-san will be staying
at my place for the first time!
Romance has refined your cuteness
to even more powerful levels.
You gush even more than I do, I think!
You guys get along so well.
I guess you don't even fight at all?
I mean, most people
fight with their SOs,
but I haven't heard
of you fighting even once.
I suppose not.
I did complain about
him being an SD once...
An SD?
He was being too considerate.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I see now.
But Tonome's a born gentleman,
so even something like
that wouldn't turn into a fight.
- True!
- I suppose!
- Hello.
- Welcome, Akira-san!
May I come in?
Do I smell roses?
Yes, I bought them on the way here.
I was so looking forward to staying
at your place, I couldn't help myself.
Thank you so much!
I'll be with Akira-san
all night in my apartment!
I have to make him feel at home!
It's a bit early for dinner, isn't it?
Oh, I suppose so...
I was so excited. Maybe I came too early?
Um... How about a nice cup of tea?
That's a good idea.
Shall I buy some tea
snacks while I'm here?
Oh, no...
I-It's a chocolate cake.
You made that yourself?!
Well... it wasn't that hard.
I've never had a partner
make sweet things for me!
Really?!
I-It's not that impressive...
Let's eat it right now.
- It makes me so happy!
- Of course!
Oh, and I have whipped cream
to go with the cake!
- Wait just a minute!
- Of course.
I've got the cream right here!
I'll make the tea too.
Do you have a vase or a glass?
I was thinking I'd put the roses in it.
Oh, there's a glass—
Hold very still.
We don't want to get
cream on your outfit.
I-I can lick it off myself!
But it's all over your hair.
All right. Look at me.
Is it cold?
- N-No.
- Good.
Akira-san's hands are so kind!
My heart can't take it!
Is she upset?
Do you have any whipping
cream left in your fridge?
- Yes.
- Would you like to remake it together?
Yes! Of course!
We'll do that, then.
There, all clean.
Thank you very much.
- It's delicious.
- Thank goodness!
It goes well with
the black tea, too. I love it.
What could be better than this?
To think this happiness
could continue all night...
Akira-san. You're quite stubborn.
As are you.
I insist that I sleep on the floor!
I cannot allow you to sleep on the floor!
I'll definitely step on you
when I have to get up!
I don't care about that! I prefer it!
What?!
I'll act as a footstool
when you're getting out of bed!
I don't want to wake you up!
We're at an impasse.
Then why don't we both
sleep on the floor?!
Why should we do that? We could
just sleep in the bed together...
Is it too cramped for you?
I-I suppose.
Akira-san's in my bed!
And two people
in a single is definitely...
Should I sleep on the other side
so that you don't fall out?
N-No! That's okay!
Come close to me, then. You'll fall out.
We slept together at the inn, didn't we?
You don't have to be so shy.
H-Having you so close in my usual bed...
i-it's like I'm doing something naughty!
You're cute when you're naughty.
You're making me mad!
Akira-san?
You're awake?
Good morning...
Good morning.
I made coffee. Would you like one?
Thank you.
I was too nervous to get much sleep.
I had to go to the bathroom too...
I'm so glad I slept on the outside.
Oh, I know.
Should we pay a visit to your parents?
I was thinking it might be time.
What do you think?
A-Are...
Are we getting married now?!
No, but I thought we should let
them know we'll be living together...
O-Of course. Yes, of course!
I jumped to conclusions again!
I love it when you get your hopes up.
It makes me appreciate how cute you are.
Y-You shouldn't love that!
A-Anyway, I'm going to call my mom.
Right. Let's set up a time.
- So, you know...
- Yes?
Before Akira-san
and I move in together...
can we pay you a visit?
Of course! Your father
and Fu-kun will be here, too!
Great! See you then!
Okay!
- What was that about?
- Oh, Fu-kun!
Was that big sis?
Yes, she's coming to visit!
- At last, this day is finally here!
- What day?
She's bringing a boyfriend home!
Understood.
I can't wait to stand face-to-face
and get his measure.
Stop that, now! He's a good man.
Welcome, Tonome-san!
Say hello, Fu-kun!
Fu-kun's here too? It's been so long!
Akira-san, Fu-kun's my little brother!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
No face, then.
Well, I do actually have one...
Let's move out!
Being in the old family
car is so relaxing!
Do you two ever go out for drives?
He's really staring at me.
Um, is Fu-kun a nickname?
Futa. I'm in my second year of high school.
Do you not often meet invisible people?
Yeah. I guess.
And why do you have that bat?
- No need to worry about that. Yet.
- "Yet"?
We'll be there soon!
All right! Here we are!
My, this is the house you grew up in?
The mosaic art tiling is beautiful!
Fu-kun and I made that a long time ago!
It lets me know
the entrance step is just ahead.
I see.
And it's not so uneven
that it could trip you up.
They made it as a summer
handicrafts project.
Yeah. With Dad.
It sounds like a wonderful memory.
I'd love to hear more like that.
Let's get an album, then!
You'll have plenty of time
for that later, so let's save it!
Come on inside!
Well, shall we go to my room first?
- Yes, let's.
- I'm coming, too.
That's okay with you, right, Tonome-san?
- You're so pushy, Fu-kun.
- Is it a problem?
I don't mind.
Fu-kun! Take them drinks!
Shizuka-san. Let me
help you up the stairs.
I can handle it!
It's my own house.
I know what I'm doing.
Oh, do you?
I do!
- Then I'll stick right behind you.
- You'd better!
This is my room.
It's so beautifully minimalist!
Shall I take your coat?
I can put it on a hanger.
Thank you.
Akira-san is in my childhood
home! It feels so strange!
He's really staring at me.
Excuse me, Futa-san.
Do you have any questions for me?
You've seemed rather interested in me...
Why's that?
Well, every time I look at you,
we make eye contact.
And you've been staring at me,
so I thought you had a question...
Did you think I didn't
notice you staring?
Well... how could I make eye contact?
I don't know where your face
or your eyes are!
True, I am invisible.
So you can look wherever you want all
the time! That's cheating!
Hey! You're the one looking at him!
Well, it is handy
when you're a detective.
Welcome back!
Shizuka's boyfriend is here.
I think my dad's home!
Well, would you like
to say hello to him now?
But he only just got back, so...
When do you think we should go down?
I'm going to the bathroom.
R-Right!
Hey, should they come down now?
We've ordered takeout,
so we'll call them down when it's here.
Sure thing.
The sushi is here!
I'm Akira Tonome.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Sit here.
R-Right!
Now, eat as much as you like!
Let's eat.
- Let's eat!
- Let's eat.
I'll put your favorites
in front of you, Shizuka.
He seems a lot like Futa-kun.
- You drink?
- Y-Yes.
You're the owner
of Shizuka's workplace, yes?
Yes. Though it's a very small agency...
Thank you. I'll try it.
This is awkward.
And he's staring at me
as intensely as Futa-kun did.
What do I do? I hope I didn't
say something to offend him...
Can you handle whiskey?
I'm sorry! He's a hard man to read!
He's been looking
forward to sharing a drink
with his daughter's
special someone for ages!
Straight, on the rocks, or diluted?
Rocks, please.
It's delicious.
Want to see my daughter as a kid?
I've made a compilation of her
pictures and videos I can run.
- Oh, I'd love that!
- Be right back.
Thanks for the food. I'm taking a bath.
Sis, get ready to take
your bath and sleep, too.
- Right!
- Tonome-san, good luck.
My husband's family memorial
video is five hours long!
Th-That's quite impressive!
I'll play it now.
Ah, yes.
This is the hospital
where my daughter was born...
She's adorable!
She didn't want anyone
but her mother in those hours.
I'm sorry to turn a day trip
into an overnight stay.
It's fine.
You can't stop my husband
when he gets his movie rolling!
- Will you leave after breakfast?
- Yeah!
I'll drive you to the station.
I know! There's a delicious
bakery on the way back!
You can buy yourselves some lunch!
What bakery is that?
It's new! You can get—
Excuse me!
Shizuka-san and I have been
dating for some time,
and we're hoping to move
in together soon, so...
That's right! We came here
to tell them that!
Of course we're fine with it!
- Right, dear?
- Yep.
Move in together?
Dad, did you already know?
Yes, I told him that's
why you were coming!
You didn't tell me.
I thought she was
just introducing him...
Didn't I? I did tell your father...
W-Well, now that we're
on the same page...
I hope to continue our acquaintance.
We feel the same way!
No one told me.
I was so nervous!
I-I'm sorry about that.
I haven't been home in so long,
I fell back into old routines...
Well, it was so hard to find
the right moment to say it, too...
B-But they're totally on board
with it! Isn't that nice?
Yes.
I don't think I've ever heard
Akira-san so nervous before!
Next, I think I should
introduce you to my pare—
A-Are you all right? Was it too hot?
N-No...
I forgot. But of course!
I have to meet his parents,
too! Of course I do!
I'd already met your mother,
which made things a bit more comfortable,
but you haven't met my
parents even once, so...
Y-Yes.
How should we approach it?
Should we put it off longer?
No! I definitely want to meet them!
I was raised in a city
with a lot of diverse species,
but my parents since
moved back to our hometown.
It's rather far, so we
may have to stay over.
- Is that all right?
- Of course!
But it's a rather particular place, so...
It's the invisible person village.
Only our kind live there.
The invisible person... village?
EPISODE 10: BEFORE WE MOVE IN TOGETHER
TO BE CONTINUED